{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121042234","data":{"timestamp":" 947121042234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121043197","data":{"timestamp":" 947121043197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121046087","data":{"timestamp":" 947121046087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121046620","data":{"timestamp":" 947121046620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121047263","data":{"timestamp":" 947121047263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121051349","data":{"timestamp":" 947121051349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121052272","data":{"timestamp":" 947121052272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121055892","data":{"timestamp":" 947121055891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121056688","data":{"timestamp":" 947121056687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121057674","data":{"timestamp":" 947121057673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121061540","data":{"timestamp":" 947121061539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121062515","data":{"timestamp":" 947121062514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121065509","data":{"timestamp":" 947121065509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121066053","data":{"timestamp":" 947121066053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121066707","data":{"timestamp":" 947121066706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121070864","data":{"timestamp":" 947121070864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121071797","data":{"timestamp":" 947121071796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121075435","data":{"timestamp":" 947121075435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121076220","data":{"timestamp":" 947121076219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121077193","data":{"timestamp":" 947121077192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121080549","data":{"timestamp":" 947121080549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121080606","data":{"timestamp":" 947121080606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 059d2179-9eaa-40c6-91cc-c1fbfb94853b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121088769","data":{"timestamp":" 947121088769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ef3b7766-b735-47c9-8158-2c07ef6d840f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121094859","data":{"timestamp":" 947121094859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ef3b7766-b735-47c9-8158-2c07ef6d840f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121126514","data":{"timestamp":" 947121126514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ef3b7766-b735-47c9-8158-2c07ef6d840f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121185535","data":{"timestamp":" 947121185535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ef3b7766-b735-47c9-8158-2c07ef6d840f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121238500","data":{"timestamp":" 947121238500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ef3b7766-b735-47c9-8158-2c07ef6d840f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121258035","data":{"timestamp":" 947121258035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ef3b7766-b735-47c9-8158-2c07ef6d840f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121259060","data":{"timestamp":" 947121259060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ef3b7766-b735-47c9-8158-2c07ef6d840f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121264614","data":{"timestamp":" 947121264613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ef3b7766-b735-47c9-8158-2c07ef6d840f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121277966","data":{"timestamp":" 947121277966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121285035","data":{"timestamp":" 947121285035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121293199","data":{"timestamp":" 947121293199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121298851","data":{"timestamp":" 947121298851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121306882","data":{"timestamp":" 947121306882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" mpaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121313008","data":{"timestamp":" 947121313008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121319601","data":{"timestamp":" 947121319601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121326468","data":{"timestamp":" 947121326468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121331835","data":{"timestamp":" 947121331835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121337450","data":{"timestamp":" 947121337450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121343718","data":{"timestamp":" 947121343718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121347912","data":{"timestamp":" 947121347911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 189804c6-ed4a-4cc1-a98a-3973defbea88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121364647","data":{"timestamp":" 947121364647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121373494","data":{"timestamp":" 947121373494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121380303","data":{"timestamp":" 947121380303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121391762","data":{"timestamp":" 947121391762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121401256","data":{"timestamp":" 947121401256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121437124","data":{"timestamp":" 947121437124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121481985","data":{"timestamp":" 947121481985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121503115","data":{"timestamp":" 947121503114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121511677","data":{"timestamp":" 947121511677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 9bbf6935-568e-440e-b543-d4cbe391d44b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121537230","data":{"timestamp":" 947121537229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121539511","data":{"timestamp":" 947121539510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121541510","data":{"timestamp":" 947121541510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121543367","data":{"timestamp":" 947121543367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121545375","data":{"timestamp":" 947121545375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121547091","data":{"timestamp":" 947121547091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121548979","data":{"timestamp":" 947121548979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121549423","data":{"timestamp":" 947121549422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121549776","data":{"timestamp":" 947121549775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121550518","data":{"timestamp":" 947121550518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121551051","data":{"timestamp":" 947121551051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121551524","data":{"timestamp":" 947121551524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121554263","data":{"timestamp":" 947121554263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121557611","data":{"timestamp":" 947121557611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121559588","data":{"timestamp":" 947121559588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121561954","data":{"timestamp":" 947121561954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121564012","data":{"timestamp":" 947121564012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121566383","data":{"timestamp":" 947121566383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121568308","data":{"timestamp":" 947121568308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121570172","data":{"timestamp":" 947121570172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121572181","data":{"timestamp":" 947121572181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121572816","data":{"timestamp":" 947121572815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121573530","data":{"timestamp":" 947121573529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121573724","data":{"timestamp":" 947121573723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121574177","data":{"timestamp":" 947121574177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121574420","data":{"timestamp":" 947121574419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121574919","data":{"timestamp":" 947121574918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121575910","data":{"timestamp":" 947121575909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121579794","data":{"timestamp":" 947121579793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAHITAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121583978","data":{"timestamp":" 947121583978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121585719","data":{"timestamp":" 947121585719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121588076","data":{"timestamp":" 947121588075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121590017","data":{"timestamp":" 947121590017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121592005","data":{"timestamp":" 947121592005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121594378","data":{"timestamp":" 947121594377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINATOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121596082","data":{"timestamp":" 947121596082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121597982","data":{"timestamp":" 947121597981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121600127","data":{"timestamp":" 947121600127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAHITAJI"," userResponse":" NAHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121600649","data":{"timestamp":" 947121600648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONE"," userResponse":" TONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121600828","data":{"timestamp":" 947121600828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121601486","data":{"timestamp":" 947121601484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121602101","data":{"timestamp":" 947121602100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121602453","data":{"timestamp":" 947121602453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121603257","data":{"timestamp":" 947121603257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINATOKA"," userResponse":" LINATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121603750","data":{"timestamp":" 947121603750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121604354","data":{"timestamp":" 947121604354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121608774","data":{"timestamp":" 947121608774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121610901","data":{"timestamp":" 947121610900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121612855","data":{"timestamp":" 947121612854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121614893","data":{"timestamp":" 947121614893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121617839","data":{"timestamp":" 947121617838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEKAUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121619946","data":{"timestamp":" 947121619945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121620439","data":{"timestamp":" 947121620438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121621106","data":{"timestamp":" 947121621105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMANDE"," userResponse":" UMANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121621843","data":{"timestamp":" 947121621843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121622688","data":{"timestamp":" 947121622687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEKAUKA"," userResponse":" UMEKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121627347","data":{"timestamp":" 947121627347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISIPOKUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121628000","data":{"timestamp":" 947121628000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" START_ALILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121630393","data":{"timestamp":" 947121630393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121632652","data":{"timestamp":" 947121632652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121636013","data":{"timestamp":" 947121636013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121637953","data":{"timestamp":" 947121637953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121640039","data":{"timestamp":" 947121640039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121642216","data":{"timestamp":" 947121642216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISIPOKUNYWA"," userResponse":" NISIPOKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121642910","data":{"timestamp":" 947121642910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121644401","data":{"timestamp":" 947121644401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFA"," userResponse":" NITAKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121645623","data":{"timestamp":" 947121645622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121646088","data":{"timestamp":" 947121646088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121646762","data":{"timestamp":" 947121646762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121651096","data":{"timestamp":" 947121651095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" NIENDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121652721","data":{"timestamp":" 947121652721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121654539","data":{"timestamp":" 947121654538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121656012","data":{"timestamp":" 947121656012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121657241","data":{"timestamp":" 947121657241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121658906","data":{"timestamp":" 947121658906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121660787","data":{"timestamp":" 947121660787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121662175","data":{"timestamp":" 947121662175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121663196","data":{"timestamp":" 947121663196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121664678","data":{"timestamp":" 947121664677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121666977","data":{"timestamp":" 947121666976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121669244","data":{"timestamp":" 947121669243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121670867","data":{"timestamp":" 947121670867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121672717","data":{"timestamp":" 947121672716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121675005","data":{"timestamp":" 947121675005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121675587","data":{"timestamp":" 947121675587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" NIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121676038","data":{"timestamp":" 947121676038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121676571","data":{"timestamp":" 947121676571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121677146","data":{"timestamp":" 947121677146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAO"," userResponse":" AMBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121678021","data":{"timestamp":" 947121678021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" NILISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121678464","data":{"timestamp":" 947121678464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121678884","data":{"timestamp":" 947121678884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121682056","data":{"timestamp":" 947121682056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121687065","data":{"timestamp":" 947121687065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKUFAGILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121689919","data":{"timestamp":" 947121689919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121691823","data":{"timestamp":" 947121691823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121694223","data":{"timestamp":" 947121694223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121696241","data":{"timestamp":" 947121696241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121699253","data":{"timestamp":" 947121699253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEKIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121701443","data":{"timestamp":" 947121701443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121703829","data":{"timestamp":" 947121703827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121705561","data":{"timestamp":" 947121705561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKUFAGILIA"," userResponse":" UTAKUFAGILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121706314","data":{"timestamp":" 947121706314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121707107","data":{"timestamp":" 947121707107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121707690","data":{"timestamp":" 947121707690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121708158","data":{"timestamp":" 947121708157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121708753","data":{"timestamp":" 947121708753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEKIMA"," userResponse":" HEKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121709984","data":{"timestamp":" 947121709984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121714867","data":{"timestamp":" 947121714867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121717193","data":{"timestamp":" 947121717193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121719590","data":{"timestamp":" 947121719590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121721967","data":{"timestamp":" 947121721967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121723803","data":{"timestamp":" 947121723803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121725935","data":{"timestamp":" 947121725935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121726648","data":{"timestamp":" 947121726648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121727394","data":{"timestamp":" 947121727393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121728539","data":{"timestamp":" 947121728539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121729165","data":{"timestamp":" 947121729164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121731316","data":{"timestamp":" 947121731316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121731803","data":{"timestamp":" 947121731802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121733652","data":{"timestamp":" 947121733651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121735450","data":{"timestamp":" 947121735450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121737997","data":{"timestamp":" 947121737997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOKAUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121739629","data":{"timestamp":" 947121739629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121741289","data":{"timestamp":" 947121741289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121743540","data":{"timestamp":" 947121743540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121745618","data":{"timestamp":" 947121745618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOKAUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121747352","data":{"timestamp":" 947121747351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITA"," userResponse":" KUPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121747830","data":{"timestamp":" 947121747830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121748443","data":{"timestamp":" 947121748442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121749810","data":{"timestamp":" 947121749810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOKAUKA"," userResponse":" ZILIZOKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121750277","data":{"timestamp":" 947121750276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121750672","data":{"timestamp":" 947121750671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121751594","data":{"timestamp":" 947121751593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121752822","data":{"timestamp":" 947121752821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOKAUKA"," userResponse":" YALIYOKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121758401","data":{"timestamp":" 947121758400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121761331","data":{"timestamp":" 947121761331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121763121","data":{"timestamp":" 947121763121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWIMBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121766947","data":{"timestamp":" 947121766946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121768793","data":{"timestamp":" 947121768792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121770698","data":{"timestamp":" 947121770698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKINGURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121772496","data":{"timestamp":" 947121772496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121773369","data":{"timestamp":" 947121773369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121774102","data":{"timestamp":" 947121774102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWIMBI"," userResponse":" MAWIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121774187","data":{"timestamp":" 947121774187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121774690","data":{"timestamp":" 947121774690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121776114","data":{"timestamp":" 947121776114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKINGURUMA"," userResponse":" YAKINGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121781372","data":{"timestamp":" 947121781372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121783697","data":{"timestamp":" 947121783697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121786250","data":{"timestamp":" 947121786250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121788283","data":{"timestamp":" 947121788283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121790800","data":{"timestamp":" 947121790800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121792716","data":{"timestamp":" 947121792716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121793239","data":{"timestamp":" 947121793239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121794234","data":{"timestamp":" 947121794233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121794838","data":{"timestamp":" 947121794838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121795741","data":{"timestamp":" 947121795741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121803165","data":{"timestamp":" 947121803165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121806308","data":{"timestamp":" 947121806307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121808658","data":{"timestamp":" 947121808658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121811543","data":{"timestamp":" 947121811543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121814262","data":{"timestamp":" 947121814261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121816519","data":{"timestamp":" 947121816519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121819293","data":{"timestamp":" 947121819293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121821669","data":{"timestamp":" 947121821668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121823634","data":{"timestamp":" 947121823634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121824780","data":{"timestamp":" 947121824779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIFURAHIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121826454","data":{"timestamp":" 947121826454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121827291","data":{"timestamp":" 947121827291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121827612","data":{"timestamp":" 947121827612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIASI"," userResponse":" KIASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121827815","data":{"timestamp":" 947121827814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121828217","data":{"timestamp":" 947121828217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121828365","data":{"timestamp":" 947121828365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUONA"," userResponse":" HAKUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121828773","data":{"timestamp":" 947121828773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBI"," userResponse":" WIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121829259","data":{"timestamp":" 947121829259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121829433","data":{"timestamp":" 947121829433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIJA"," userResponse":" LIKIJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121835180","data":{"timestamp":" 947121835179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" START_ALIJARIBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121836723","data":{"timestamp":" 947121836723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" START_ZILIZOMPITA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121838515","data":{"timestamp":" 947121838514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121841012","data":{"timestamp":" 947121841012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121842850","data":{"timestamp":" 947121842850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121844657","data":{"timestamp":" 947121844657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121847428","data":{"timestamp":" 947121847428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121850257","data":{"timestamp":" 947121850257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOMPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121853003","data":{"timestamp":" 947121853003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKIELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121854881","data":{"timestamp":" 947121854881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121855825","data":{"timestamp":" 947121855824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJARIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121856476","data":{"timestamp":" 947121856475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHIKA"," userResponse":" KUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121856990","data":{"timestamp":" 947121856990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121857627","data":{"timestamp":" 947121857626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121859092","data":{"timestamp":" 947121859092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOMPITA"," userResponse":" ZILIZOMPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121860069","data":{"timestamp":" 947121860068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKIELEA"," userResponse":" ZIKIELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121863772","data":{"timestamp":" 947121863772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121866034","data":{"timestamp":" 947121866033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFAGILIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121867848","data":{"timestamp":" 947121867848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121869440","data":{"timestamp":" 947121869440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121871979","data":{"timestamp":" 947121871979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121873997","data":{"timestamp":" 947121873997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121875100","data":{"timestamp":" 947121875100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFAGILIWA"," userResponse":" ALIFAGILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121875904","data":{"timestamp":" 947121875903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121876107","data":{"timestamp":" 947121876106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121876569","data":{"timestamp":" 947121876569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121880876","data":{"timestamp":" 947121880876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121883334","data":{"timestamp":" 947121883333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121885019","data":{"timestamp":" 947121885019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121886086","data":{"timestamp":" 947121886085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANISAIDIE"," userResponse":" ANISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121889824","data":{"timestamp":" 947121889824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121892143","data":{"timestamp":" 947121892143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121894441","data":{"timestamp":" 947121894441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121895335","data":{"timestamp":" 947121895334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121898009","data":{"timestamp":" 947121898009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121900166","data":{"timestamp":" 947121900166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121901310","data":{"timestamp":" 947121901310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PANDA"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121903764","data":{"timestamp":" 947121903764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121905912","data":{"timestamp":" 947121905911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121910065","data":{"timestamp":" 947121910064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121912555","data":{"timestamp":" 947121912555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEUPE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121914534","data":{"timestamp":" 947121914534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121916334","data":{"timestamp":" 947121916334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121918345","data":{"timestamp":" 947121918345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121920923","data":{"timestamp":" 947121920923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMNYOSHEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121923662","data":{"timestamp":" 947121923662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121925922","data":{"timestamp":" 947121925922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121928886","data":{"timestamp":" 947121928886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121931147","data":{"timestamp":" 947121931147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121933801","data":{"timestamp":" 947121933801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121934541","data":{"timestamp":" 947121934540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDA"," userResponse":" PANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121934974","data":{"timestamp":" 947121934973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121935947","data":{"timestamp":" 947121935946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121936558","data":{"timestamp":" 947121936557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEUPE"," userResponse":" MWEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121937386","data":{"timestamp":" 947121937386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121938021","data":{"timestamp":" 947121938021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121938638","data":{"timestamp":" 947121938638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121939684","data":{"timestamp":" 947121939683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMNYOSHEA"," userResponse":" AMEMNYOSHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121940411","data":{"timestamp":" 947121940410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121940986","data":{"timestamp":" 947121940985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121941488","data":{"timestamp":" 947121941488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121941915","data":{"timestamp":" 947121941914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121948406","data":{"timestamp":" 947121948406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITAONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121950288","data":{"timestamp":" 947121950288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121952055","data":{"timestamp":" 947121952055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121954316","data":{"timestamp":" 947121954316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKURANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121956182","data":{"timestamp":" 947121956182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121977668","data":{"timestamp":" 947121977667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121979774","data":{"timestamp":" 947121979774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121982313","data":{"timestamp":" 947121982313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITAONDOKA"," userResponse":" SITAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121982775","data":{"timestamp":" 947121982775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121983248","data":{"timestamp":" 947121983248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" KUTOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121983862","data":{"timestamp":" 947121983862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKURANI"," userResponse":" SHUKURANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121984204","data":{"timestamp":" 947121984204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121984407","data":{"timestamp":" 947121984407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121984951","data":{"timestamp":" 947121984951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121991043","data":{"timestamp":" 947121991043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121993457","data":{"timestamp":" 947121993457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947121998143","data":{"timestamp":" 947121998143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKAPOKUJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122000199","data":{"timestamp":" 947122000199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122003120","data":{"timestamp":" 947122003120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122005485","data":{"timestamp":" 947122005485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NITASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122006598","data":{"timestamp":" 947122006598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122007572","data":{"timestamp":" 947122007572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKAPOKUJA"," userResponse":" ATAKAPOKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122007974","data":{"timestamp":" 947122007974"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122008488","data":{"timestamp":" 947122008487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitasubiri hadi atakapokuja kunywa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122015557","data":{"timestamp":" 947122015557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122017020","data":{"timestamp":" 947122017020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122021174","data":{"timestamp":" 947122021174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122023147","data":{"timestamp":" 947122023147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122026328","data":{"timestamp":" 947122026328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122036176","data":{"timestamp":" 947122036176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122038941","data":{"timestamp":" 947122038941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122041111","data":{"timestamp":" 947122041111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122045051","data":{"timestamp":" 947122045051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122047434","data":{"timestamp":" 947122047434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122054871","data":{"timestamp":" 947122054870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122056795","data":{"timestamp":" 947122056794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122057220","data":{"timestamp":" 947122057220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122058383","data":{"timestamp":" 947122058382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" ALIPOSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122059576","data":{"timestamp":" 947122059576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122060139","data":{"timestamp":" 947122060139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122060901","data":{"timestamp":" 947122060901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUJA"," userResponse":" WALIKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122061645","data":{"timestamp":" 947122061645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122062488","data":{"timestamp":" 947122062487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122062691","data":{"timestamp":" 947122062691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122063324","data":{"timestamp":" 947122063324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITEGO"," userResponse":" MITEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122063768","data":{"timestamp":" 947122063767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja aliposubiri wavulana wawili walikuja mtoni wakiwa na mitego yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122066071","data":{"timestamp":" 947122066071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122066368","data":{"timestamp":" 947122066368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122068399","data":{"timestamp":" 947122068399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122072496","data":{"timestamp":" 947122072495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEUPE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122075240","data":{"timestamp":" 947122075240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122077652","data":{"timestamp":" 947122077652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122080351","data":{"timestamp":" 947122080350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122082349","data":{"timestamp":" 947122082349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122085885","data":{"timestamp":" 947122085885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122090572","data":{"timestamp":" 947122090572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122095392","data":{"timestamp":" 947122095392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122100675","data":{"timestamp":" 947122100675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122102235","data":{"timestamp":" 947122102235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122102938","data":{"timestamp":" 947122102937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122103580","data":{"timestamp":" 947122103580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122104244","data":{"timestamp":" 947122104244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEUPE"," userResponse":" MWEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122105099","data":{"timestamp":" 947122105098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYE"," userResponse":" AMBAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122105492","data":{"timestamp":" 947122105492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJA"," userResponse":" HUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122105836","data":{"timestamp":" 947122105836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122106269","data":{"timestamp":" 947122106269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122106802","data":{"timestamp":" 947122106802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122107788","data":{"timestamp":" 947122107788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122108342","data":{"timestamp":" 947122108342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122109126","data":{"timestamp":" 947122109125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna Njiwa mmoja mweupe ambaye huja hapa kunywa maji mvulana mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122112024","data":{"timestamp":" 947122112024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAMLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122113717","data":{"timestamp":" 947122113717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122117108","data":{"timestamp":" 947122117108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122119260","data":{"timestamp":" 947122119260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122121059","data":{"timestamp":" 947122121059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122123265","data":{"timestamp":" 947122123265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAMLA"," userResponse":" TUTAMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122123687","data":{"timestamp":" 947122123686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122124231","data":{"timestamp":" 947122124230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122124453","data":{"timestamp":" 947122124453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122125123","data":{"timestamp":" 947122125123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122135910","data":{"timestamp":" 947122135910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122136004","data":{"timestamp":" 947122136004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122174874","data":{"timestamp":" 947122174874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fb50626f-0b38-49a4-8b90-a94746335181"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tutamla kwa chakula cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122189185","data":{"timestamp":" 947122189185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122195383","data":{"timestamp":" 947122195383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122196274","data":{"timestamp":" 947122196274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vu"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122196949","data":{"timestamp":" 947122196949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122215207","data":{"timestamp":" 947122215207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_udongo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122218214","data":{"timestamp":" 947122218214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_udongo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122219556","data":{"timestamp":" 947122219555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_udongo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngo"," userResponse":" ngo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122234085","data":{"timestamp":" 947122234084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122235635","data":{"timestamp":" 947122235634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122236632","data":{"timestamp":" 947122236631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122247346","data":{"timestamp":" 947122247345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiboko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122248903","data":{"timestamp":" 947122248902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiboko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122249718","data":{"timestamp":" 947122249718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiboko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122254292","data":{"timestamp":" 947122254292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_uyoga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122254923","data":{"timestamp":" 947122254923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_uyoga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yo"," userResponse":" yo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122255798","data":{"timestamp":" 947122255798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_uyoga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122259199","data":{"timestamp":" 947122259198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122259946","data":{"timestamp":" 947122259946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyo"," userResponse":" nyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122260704","data":{"timestamp":" 947122260704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122264630","data":{"timestamp":" 947122264629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_elimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122266069","data":{"timestamp":" 947122266068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_elimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122267320","data":{"timestamp":" 947122267320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_elimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122280606","data":{"timestamp":" 947122280606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122281603","data":{"timestamp":" 947122281603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122282445","data":{"timestamp":" 947122282445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122286347","data":{"timestamp":" 947122286347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kalamu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122287792","data":{"timestamp":" 947122287792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kalamu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122288917","data":{"timestamp":" 947122288917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kalamu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122292699","data":{"timestamp":" 947122292699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gunia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" gu"," userResponse":" gu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122294589","data":{"timestamp":" 947122294589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gunia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122295447","data":{"timestamp":" 947122295447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gunia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122297441","data":{"timestamp":" 947122297440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" f4b6f2e1-1233-4526-bcac-cd489ed22a4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_gunia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122317831","data":{"timestamp":" 947122317830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jekundu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" je"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122324109","data":{"timestamp":" 947122324109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jekundu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" je"," userResponse":" je"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122324950","data":{"timestamp":" 947122324950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jekundu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122331490","data":{"timestamp":" 947122331490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jekundu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122332423","data":{"timestamp":" 947122332423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jekundu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122336465","data":{"timestamp":" 947122336465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122337187","data":{"timestamp":" 947122337187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndo"," userResponse":" ndo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122337895","data":{"timestamp":" 947122337895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kondoo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122342488","data":{"timestamp":" 947122342487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122343754","data":{"timestamp":" 947122343754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122345468","data":{"timestamp":" 947122345467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122366912","data":{"timestamp":" 947122366912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiboko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122367818","data":{"timestamp":" 947122367818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiboko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122368868","data":{"timestamp":" 947122368868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiboko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122371042","data":{"timestamp":" 947122371042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chakula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122376024","data":{"timestamp":" 947122376024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chakula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122377268","data":{"timestamp":" 947122377268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chakula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122380866","data":{"timestamp":" 947122380865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chakula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122385638","data":{"timestamp":" 947122385638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_endesha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122386479","data":{"timestamp":" 947122386479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_endesha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122387470","data":{"timestamp":" 947122387470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_endesha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sha"," userResponse":" sha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122392104","data":{"timestamp":" 947122392104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fagio"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122393026","data":{"timestamp":" 947122393026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fagio"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" gi"," userResponse":" gi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122393901","data":{"timestamp":" 947122393901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fagio"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122399284","data":{"timestamp":" 947122399284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_redio"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" re"," userResponse":" re"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122400274","data":{"timestamp":" 947122400273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_redio"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" di"," userResponse":" di"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122401073","data":{"timestamp":" 947122401073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_redio"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122405673","data":{"timestamp":" 947122405673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baridi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122406746","data":{"timestamp":" 947122406746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baridi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" di"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122413020","data":{"timestamp":" 947122413020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baridi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122414485","data":{"timestamp":" 947122414485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baridi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" di"," userResponse":" di"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122420210","data":{"timestamp":" 947122420210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zawadi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122426548","data":{"timestamp":" 947122426548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zawadi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122428047","data":{"timestamp":" 947122428047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zawadi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122429307","data":{"timestamp":" 947122429307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zawadi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" di"," userResponse":" di"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122431093","data":{"timestamp":" 947122431092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" ab20b1ce-39f8-474e-b65e-c0749562a0c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_zawadi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122440823","data":{"timestamp":" 947122440823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122441055","data":{"timestamp":" 947122441055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122442018","data":{"timestamp":" 947122442018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122443291","data":{"timestamp":" 947122443291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122446204","data":{"timestamp":" 947122446204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122447048","data":{"timestamp":" 947122447048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122447361","data":{"timestamp":" 947122447361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122448593","data":{"timestamp":" 947122448592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122452124","data":{"timestamp":" 947122452124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122453108","data":{"timestamp":" 947122453108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122453361","data":{"timestamp":" 947122453361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122454303","data":{"timestamp":" 947122454303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122457132","data":{"timestamp":" 947122457132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122458165","data":{"timestamp":" 947122458165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122458637","data":{"timestamp":" 947122458637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122463153","data":{"timestamp":" 947122463153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122463214","data":{"timestamp":" 947122463213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 64c64704-5827-4e51-b64b-e961ef819452"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122474616","data":{"timestamp":" 947122474616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122475233","data":{"timestamp":" 947122475233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122487624","data":{"timestamp":" 947122487624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122513571","data":{"timestamp":" 947122513571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlango"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122514768","data":{"timestamp":" 947122514768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlango"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122515468","data":{"timestamp":" 947122515468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlango"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngo"," userResponse":" ngo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122532999","data":{"timestamp":" 947122532999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_andazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122533970","data":{"timestamp":" 947122533970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_andazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122534887","data":{"timestamp":" 947122534887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_andazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122539338","data":{"timestamp":" 947122539337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122539969","data":{"timestamp":" 947122539969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122540519","data":{"timestamp":" 947122540519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" no"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122544287","data":{"timestamp":" 947122544287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_andika"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122544818","data":{"timestamp":" 947122544817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_andika"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndi"," userResponse":" ndi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122545459","data":{"timestamp":" 947122545459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_andika"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122557293","data":{"timestamp":" 947122557293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122558515","data":{"timestamp":" 947122558515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122559213","data":{"timestamp":" 947122559213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122563817","data":{"timestamp":" 947122563816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_elimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122564704","data":{"timestamp":" 947122564703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_elimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122565295","data":{"timestamp":" 947122565295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_elimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122569726","data":{"timestamp":" 947122569726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vidole"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122570161","data":{"timestamp":" 947122570160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vidole"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122570669","data":{"timestamp":" 947122570669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vidole"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122584644","data":{"timestamp":" 947122584644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwa"," userResponse":" kwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122585322","data":{"timestamp":" 947122585322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122585831","data":{"timestamp":" 947122585830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122593864","data":{"timestamp":" 947122593863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_laini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122600302","data":{"timestamp":" 947122600302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_laini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122600968","data":{"timestamp":" 947122600968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_laini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122601418","data":{"timestamp":" 947122601418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_laini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122603108","data":{"timestamp":" 947122603107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_laini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122613525","data":{"timestamp":" 947122613525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 1a204737-1a0c-456c-8694-b381d9ed2d9c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_laini"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122626397","data":{"timestamp":" 947122626396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122626982","data":{"timestamp":" 947122626982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122628076","data":{"timestamp":" 947122628076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPITA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122629080","data":{"timestamp":" 947122629079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122629269","data":{"timestamp":" 947122629268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122629718","data":{"timestamp":" 947122629717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122630483","data":{"timestamp":" 947122630482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122631456","data":{"timestamp":" 947122631456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122634595","data":{"timestamp":" 947122634595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122636970","data":{"timestamp":" 947122636970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122639266","data":{"timestamp":" 947122639266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122641402","data":{"timestamp":" 947122641402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122643167","data":{"timestamp":" 947122643167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122645223","data":{"timestamp":" 947122645222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122647536","data":{"timestamp":" 947122647536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122650843","data":{"timestamp":" 947122650842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122652666","data":{"timestamp":" 947122652666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122653322","data":{"timestamp":" 947122653322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122654500","data":{"timestamp":" 947122654500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122655449","data":{"timestamp":" 947122655449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122656224","data":{"timestamp":" 947122656224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122657029","data":{"timestamp":" 947122657028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPENZI"," userResponse":" WAPENZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122657854","data":{"timestamp":" 947122657853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122660234","data":{"timestamp":" 947122660234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122661694","data":{"timestamp":" 947122661694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122664269","data":{"timestamp":" 947122664269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122666471","data":{"timestamp":" 947122666471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122672020","data":{"timestamp":" 947122672020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122675603","data":{"timestamp":" 947122675603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPENZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122677791","data":{"timestamp":" 947122677791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122680051","data":{"timestamp":" 947122680050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122681136","data":{"timestamp":" 947122681135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122681770","data":{"timestamp":" 947122681770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122682559","data":{"timestamp":" 947122682558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" WIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122683086","data":{"timestamp":" 947122683085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122683468","data":{"timestamp":" 947122683467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122684001","data":{"timestamp":" 947122684000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122684382","data":{"timestamp":" 947122684382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122685902","data":{"timestamp":" 947122685901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMETAMETA"," userResponse":" ILIMETAMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122686442","data":{"timestamp":" 947122686440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122687345","data":{"timestamp":" 947122687345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" KUVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122690821","data":{"timestamp":" 947122690821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122691904","data":{"timestamp":" 947122691904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122691907","data":{"timestamp":" 947122691907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122692577","data":{"timestamp":" 947122692577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122694742","data":{"timestamp":" 947122694742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122696373","data":{"timestamp":" 947122696373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122698163","data":{"timestamp":" 947122698163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122700291","data":{"timestamp":" 947122700291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122702056","data":{"timestamp":" 947122702056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122704482","data":{"timestamp":" 947122704481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMETAMETA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122707332","data":{"timestamp":" 947122707332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122709243","data":{"timestamp":" 947122709243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122711864","data":{"timestamp":" 947122711864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122713071","data":{"timestamp":" 947122713070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122713773","data":{"timestamp":" 947122713772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122714254","data":{"timestamp":" 947122714253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122715141","data":{"timestamp":" 947122715141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONEKANA"," userResponse":" UKAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122715666","data":{"timestamp":" 947122715666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122716566","data":{"timestamp":" 947122716565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122719638","data":{"timestamp":" 947122719638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122721352","data":{"timestamp":" 947122721352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122723346","data":{"timestamp":" 947122723346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122726239","data":{"timestamp":" 947122726239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122729023","data":{"timestamp":" 947122729023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONEKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122730934","data":{"timestamp":" 947122730934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122733089","data":{"timestamp":" 947122733089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122734770","data":{"timestamp":" 947122734769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122736060","data":{"timestamp":" 947122736059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIANGALIE"," userResponse":" NIANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122736962","data":{"timestamp":" 947122736962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122737439","data":{"timestamp":" 947122737439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" SURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122738143","data":{"timestamp":" 947122738143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122738557","data":{"timestamp":" 947122738557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122742991","data":{"timestamp":" 947122742991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122745600","data":{"timestamp":" 947122745599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIANGALIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122747438","data":{"timestamp":" 947122747438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122749380","data":{"timestamp":" 947122749379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122750961","data":{"timestamp":" 947122750961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122753344","data":{"timestamp":" 947122753343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122755645","data":{"timestamp":" 947122755644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122756124","data":{"timestamp":" 947122756124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122756878","data":{"timestamp":" 947122756877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122757678","data":{"timestamp":" 947122757677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122758282","data":{"timestamp":" 947122758281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122759097","data":{"timestamp":" 947122759097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122762800","data":{"timestamp":" 947122762799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122768315","data":{"timestamp":" 947122768314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122771742","data":{"timestamp":" 947122771741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122774859","data":{"timestamp":" 947122774859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122777677","data":{"timestamp":" 947122777677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122780880","data":{"timestamp":" 947122780879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122783544","data":{"timestamp":" 947122783543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122784447","data":{"timestamp":" 947122784446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122785966","data":{"timestamp":" 947122785965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKILIZA"," userResponse":" SIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122790468","data":{"timestamp":" 947122790467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122793393","data":{"timestamp":" 947122793392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122797173","data":{"timestamp":" 947122797172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKILIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122799061","data":{"timestamp":" 947122799061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIA"," userResponse":" TIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122799728","data":{"timestamp":" 947122799727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122800797","data":{"timestamp":" 947122800797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122801609","data":{"timestamp":" 947122801608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122802518","data":{"timestamp":" 947122802518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEKE"," userResponse":" UKIWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122803267","data":{"timestamp":" 947122803266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKONI"," userResponse":" MEKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122806727","data":{"timestamp":" 947122806725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122810490","data":{"timestamp":" 947122810488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122814096","data":{"timestamp":" 947122814095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122817290","data":{"timestamp":" 947122817290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122821525","data":{"timestamp":" 947122821524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122824901","data":{"timestamp":" 947122824900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122827230","data":{"timestamp":" 947122827230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122827301","data":{"timestamp":" 947122827300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122831778","data":{"timestamp":" 947122831778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122835096","data":{"timestamp":" 947122835095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122837937","data":{"timestamp":" 947122837930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122838366","data":{"timestamp":" 947122838365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122839046","data":{"timestamp":" 947122839045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122839868","data":{"timestamp":" 947122839867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122840619","data":{"timestamp":" 947122840619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122841480","data":{"timestamp":" 947122841480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122844766","data":{"timestamp":" 947122844765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122845075","data":{"timestamp":" 947122845074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122847321","data":{"timestamp":" 947122847321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" START_AKASEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122851374","data":{"timestamp":" 947122851373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122854701","data":{"timestamp":" 947122854699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122857291","data":{"timestamp":" 947122857291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122860508","data":{"timestamp":" 947122860507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122862434","data":{"timestamp":" 947122862431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FYATA"," userResponse":" FYATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122863285","data":{"timestamp":" 947122863284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMI"," userResponse":" ULIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122863807","data":{"timestamp":" 947122863807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122864168","data":{"timestamp":" 947122864168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122867590","data":{"timestamp":" 947122867589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FYATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122870076","data":{"timestamp":" 947122870075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122873659","data":{"timestamp":" 947122873658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122875947","data":{"timestamp":" 947122875946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122877784","data":{"timestamp":" 947122877783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122879322","data":{"timestamp":" 947122879321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" AKAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122883013","data":{"timestamp":" 947122883012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122886111","data":{"timestamp":" 947122886111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122888761","data":{"timestamp":" 947122888753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122889431","data":{"timestamp":" 947122889424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122890222","data":{"timestamp":" 947122890221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122891085","data":{"timestamp":" 947122891084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122891457","data":{"timestamp":" 947122891457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122892104","data":{"timestamp":" 947122892102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIA"," userResponse":" KUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122892598","data":{"timestamp":" 947122892596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122893437","data":{"timestamp":" 947122893434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122896643","data":{"timestamp":" 947122896642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122899474","data":{"timestamp":" 947122899474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122902357","data":{"timestamp":" 947122902356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122906699","data":{"timestamp":" 947122906699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122909059","data":{"timestamp":" 947122909058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122912527","data":{"timestamp":" 947122912526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122916037","data":{"timestamp":" 947122916036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122920765","data":{"timestamp":" 947122920763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122921714","data":{"timestamp":" 947122921713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122923638","data":{"timestamp":" 947122923637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122923728","data":{"timestamp":" 947122923727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPOANZA"," userResponse":" YALIPOANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122924517","data":{"timestamp":" 947122924517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEMKA"," userResponse":" KUCHEMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122924647","data":{"timestamp":" 947122924646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," userResponse":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122925161","data":{"timestamp":" 947122925161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122931809","data":{"timestamp":" 947122931808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122935255","data":{"timestamp":" 947122935254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPOANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122938497","data":{"timestamp":" 947122938497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122942456","data":{"timestamp":" 947122942456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122946297","data":{"timestamp":" 947122946296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122948483","data":{"timestamp":" 947122948475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122949077","data":{"timestamp":" 947122949077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122949538","data":{"timestamp":" 947122949537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122950745","data":{"timestamp":" 947122950744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKACHOMEKA"," userResponse":" IKACHOMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122951223","data":{"timestamp":" 947122951221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122951775","data":{"timestamp":" 947122951768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122952224","data":{"timestamp":" 947122952223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122953288","data":{"timestamp":" 947122953287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAKATIKA"," userResponse":" UKAKATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122957203","data":{"timestamp":" 947122957202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122960338","data":{"timestamp":" 947122960337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122963618","data":{"timestamp":" 947122963617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122966713","data":{"timestamp":" 947122966712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKACHOMEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122968980","data":{"timestamp":" 947122968979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122972152","data":{"timestamp":" 947122972151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122975122","data":{"timestamp":" 947122975122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122978309","data":{"timestamp":" 947122978308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAKATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122980523","data":{"timestamp":" 947122980523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122981136","data":{"timestamp":" 947122981136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADALA"," userResponse":" BADALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122981440","data":{"timestamp":" 947122981439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122982496","data":{"timestamp":" 947122982496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMETAMETA"," userResponse":" KUMETAMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122982705","data":{"timestamp":" 947122982704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122983121","data":{"timestamp":" 947122983119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122983787","data":{"timestamp":" 947122983786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122984217","data":{"timestamp":" 947122984217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122984934","data":{"timestamp":" 947122984933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122986232","data":{"timestamp":" 947122986231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122986572","data":{"timestamp":" 947122986571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122987195","data":{"timestamp":" 947122987194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" SURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122988065","data":{"timestamp":" 947122988064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122988739","data":{"timestamp":" 947122988738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122992926","data":{"timestamp":" 947122992925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122995885","data":{"timestamp":" 947122995884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947122998130","data":{"timestamp":" 947122998129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123001873","data":{"timestamp":" 947123001872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMETAMETA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123004155","data":{"timestamp":" 947123004154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123007310","data":{"timestamp":" 947123007307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123010243","data":{"timestamp":" 947123010243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123012849","data":{"timestamp":" 947123012849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123015205","data":{"timestamp":" 947123015204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123018567","data":{"timestamp":" 947123018566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123021270","data":{"timestamp":" 947123021269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123024239","data":{"timestamp":" 947123024239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123026478","data":{"timestamp":" 947123026477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123029467","data":{"timestamp":" 947123029466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123031548","data":{"timestamp":" 947123031547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123032289","data":{"timestamp":" 947123032289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123040622","data":{"timestamp":" 947123040617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 8f67e14a-bb18-4ab9-a043-dc71a36dada3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123086211","data":{"timestamp":" 947123086210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123087912","data":{"timestamp":" 947123087911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123089268","data":{"timestamp":" 947123089268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_farasi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123095911","data":{"timestamp":" 947123095910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123098598","data":{"timestamp":" 947123098598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123100463","data":{"timestamp":" 947123100462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123108263","data":{"timestamp":" 947123108262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123109544","data":{"timestamp":" 947123109543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123110512","data":{"timestamp":" 947123110511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123115716","data":{"timestamp":" 947123115711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_viatu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123117096","data":{"timestamp":" 947123117096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_viatu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123118644","data":{"timestamp":" 947123118643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_viatu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123125626","data":{"timestamp":" 947123125625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ingia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123126645","data":{"timestamp":" 947123126644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ingia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngi"," userResponse":" ngi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123128270","data":{"timestamp":" 947123128269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ingia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123140408","data":{"timestamp":" 947123140407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_godoro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123141662","data":{"timestamp":" 947123141661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_godoro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123149100","data":{"timestamp":" 947123149099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_godoro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123150304","data":{"timestamp":" 947123150299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_godoro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123155264","data":{"timestamp":" 947123155262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_karoti"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123157696","data":{"timestamp":" 947123157695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_karoti"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123158507","data":{"timestamp":" 947123158502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_karoti"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123163753","data":{"timestamp":" 947123163739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwa"," userResponse":" kwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123164541","data":{"timestamp":" 947123164540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123165204","data":{"timestamp":" 947123165203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123169727","data":{"timestamp":" 947123169726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ramani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123182023","data":{"timestamp":" 947123182023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ramani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123183418","data":{"timestamp":" 947123183417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ramani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123184175","data":{"timestamp":" 947123184174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ramani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123196220","data":{"timestamp":" 947123196219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123197267","data":{"timestamp":" 947123197266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123198061","data":{"timestamp":" 947123198060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123200975","data":{"timestamp":" 947123200974"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123237513","data":{"timestamp":" 947123237512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123253783","data":{"timestamp":" 947123253782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123267011","data":{"timestamp":" 947123267010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" fcf3c215-81fd-48a3-a1c5-64de9d583ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123287332","data":{"timestamp":" 947123287331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123288407","data":{"timestamp":" 947123288404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123289808","data":{"timestamp":" 947123289807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAAMKA"," userResponse":" ANAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123290694","data":{"timestamp":" 947123290688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123291656","data":{"timestamp":" 947123291655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123292263","data":{"timestamp":" 947123292262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123293212","data":{"timestamp":" 947123293209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123297583","data":{"timestamp":" 947123297582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" START_YAYERI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123299787","data":{"timestamp":" 947123299785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123300574","data":{"timestamp":" 947123300573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" db060508-74f9-4088-becd-b126a9e7f1a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" START_YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123330145","data":{"timestamp":" 947123330144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 392908de-a4f8-42e4-a58d-fcba2010ad3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123330626","data":{"timestamp":" 947123330625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 392908de-a4f8-42e4-a58d-fcba2010ad3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_1+3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123350112","data":{"timestamp":" 947123350106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fagio"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123351177","data":{"timestamp":" 947123351176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fagio"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" gi"," userResponse":" gi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123352039","data":{"timestamp":" 947123352038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fagio"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123357984","data":{"timestamp":" 947123357983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123358955","data":{"timestamp":" 947123358953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nga"," userResponse":" nga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123359517","data":{"timestamp":" 947123359516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123365663","data":{"timestamp":" 947123365662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123366376","data":{"timestamp":" 947123366375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123366882","data":{"timestamp":" 947123366881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kikombe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123373269","data":{"timestamp":" 947123373229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nanasi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123374167","data":{"timestamp":" 947123374166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nanasi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123374804","data":{"timestamp":" 947123374803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nanasi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123382219","data":{"timestamp":" 947123382210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123383006","data":{"timestamp":" 947123383005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123383571","data":{"timestamp":" 947123383562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123398430","data":{"timestamp":" 947123398429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123399967","data":{"timestamp":" 947123399966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123401402","data":{"timestamp":" 947123401401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kusoma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123413321","data":{"timestamp":" 947123413320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123415906","data":{"timestamp":" 947123415905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vu"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123416746","data":{"timestamp":" 947123416744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123426937","data":{"timestamp":" 947123426936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123427455","data":{"timestamp":" 947123427454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123427806","data":{"timestamp":" 947123427804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123434562","data":{"timestamp":" 947123434561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123435572","data":{"timestamp":" 947123435566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123436244","data":{"timestamp":" 947123436237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mdomo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123447835","data":{"timestamp":" 947123447834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_polisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123448801","data":{"timestamp":" 947123448800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_polisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123449346","data":{"timestamp":" 947123449345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_polisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123453320","data":{"timestamp":" 947123453319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_polisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123472474","data":{"timestamp":" 947123472472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 04d38a39-530f-4237-8dbd-ac8fada0567d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_polisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123495775","data":{"timestamp":" 947123495775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 517d82c9-fb95-451a-91ca-d7bdcbb423fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123496356","data":{"timestamp":" 947123496354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 517d82c9-fb95-451a-91ca-d7bdcbb423fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123498487","data":{"timestamp":" 947123498486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 517d82c9-fb95-451a-91ca-d7bdcbb423fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123518669","data":{"timestamp":" 947123518668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 517d82c9-fb95-451a-91ca-d7bdcbb423fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123543664","data":{"timestamp":" 947123543663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123544603","data":{"timestamp":" 947123544602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123545282","data":{"timestamp":" 947123545282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123545961","data":{"timestamp":" 947123545961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123546200","data":{"timestamp":" 947123546199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123546987","data":{"timestamp":" 947123546986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DASARA"," userResponse":" DASARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123560592","data":{"timestamp":" 947123560591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123565644","data":{"timestamp":" 947123565643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123570873","data":{"timestamp":" 947123570872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123574319","data":{"timestamp":" 947123574318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123578227","data":{"timestamp":" 947123578226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123581978","data":{"timestamp":" 947123581978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DASARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123585652","data":{"timestamp":" 947123585651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123587075","data":{"timestamp":" 947123587074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUNULIA"," userResponse":" ALIMNUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123587697","data":{"timestamp":" 947123587697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINTU"," userResponse":" CHINTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123588493","data":{"timestamp":" 947123588492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" MIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123588582","data":{"timestamp":" 947123588581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123589668","data":{"timestamp":" 947123589667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" KUPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123594465","data":{"timestamp":" 947123594464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123598380","data":{"timestamp":" 947123598379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUNULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123606644","data":{"timestamp":" 947123606643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123612088","data":{"timestamp":" 947123612087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123621497","data":{"timestamp":" 947123621496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123623311","data":{"timestamp":" 947123623310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" b8ec1914-4d64-4736-8883-8c7335c1fd62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123649567","data":{"timestamp":" 947123649566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123649820","data":{"timestamp":" 947123649819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123651142","data":{"timestamp":" 947123651141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123652475","data":{"timestamp":" 947123652474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123657765","data":{"timestamp":" 947123657764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123658626","data":{"timestamp":" 947123658625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123658997","data":{"timestamp":" 947123658996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123660248","data":{"timestamp":" 947123660247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123665419","data":{"timestamp":" 947123665418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123666428","data":{"timestamp":" 947123666427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123666702","data":{"timestamp":" 947123666702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123667670","data":{"timestamp":" 947123667669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123672619","data":{"timestamp":" 947123672618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123673700","data":{"timestamp":" 947123673699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123674459","data":{"timestamp":" 947123674458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123680941","data":{"timestamp":" 947123680939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947123683759","data":{"timestamp":" 947123683758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000106_041018"," gameId":" 0abd2452-ee01-408a-bc35-5e62478c9943"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}